I want to discuss a topic that I am passionate about.
So I want to talk about weaponizing the internet.
I woke up yesterday morning to an article that had been written about me on the Griot
that was really just an effort to try and get clicks.
But it was the third in a series of articles that have literally just been like,
is Amanda Seals a whack-ass person?
With no actual proof of me doing whack-ass things.
When I stepped back, because I always try to step back,
I said, why would these Black media spaces, the Griot, the Root, Essence,
why would they be using their massive platforms to push this kind of narrative?
Like, why would that be helpful?
And what it really leaned into me was, if it got clicks,
then it was like, well, let's get on the click train too.
I just feel like we're weaponizing our internet spaces for such,
like for such, like, is that it? That's all it takes?
When I was in Flowetry, Wendy Williams spent a week soliciting folks
to talk trash about Amanda Seals. A week.
Oh, really?
Yes. She spent a week. Every day, she'd be like,
if you've had a bad experience with Amanda Seals,
if you've got something to say about Amanda Seals, give us a call.
Give us a call. Not one call.
And by the end of the week, she was like, well, I tried,
but there ain't no dirt on Amanda Seals.
And I just feel like that is a testament.
I made it out of that.
I know, right? I didn't know you had that going on.
Cold world, baby. Cold world.
We are.